(The Day of the Showdown)
- Nice to see you all. - Nice to see you.
The preview of the First Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day...
aired last week and went viral.
- It did. - Right.
- It did go viral. - People are looking forward to it.
So many people commented that...
they didn't expect to see this many guests...
- Right. - and that...
they were so looking forward to it.
- The expectations are high. - That's right.
The 100m sprint between Sung Hwan and me...
initiated this chain reaction.
(Hyun Moo, do you think you can beat me?)
(It began as Sung Hwan provoked Hyun Moo.)
(Let's do a 100m sprint in front of the MBC building.)
(Hyun Moo and Sung Hwan had a race under the moonlight.)
(These two innocent middle-aged men became intensely competitive.)
(Sung Hwan's tears got Hyun Moo to promise a field day.)
(Then I hope...)
(you can be on my team, MINHO.)
(The embers of their competitiveness turned into a recruiting battle.)
(MINHO)
(To top it off,)
(Old Money came into play.)
(President Jun will pull out all the stops.)
(The day of the field day)
Who's that?
(He trudges along in the rain.)
I could tell by the gait that it was Kian84.
Why are we having a field day in a place like this?
(This is the spot they will assemble for the field day?)
(A curious facial expression)
I was surprised that you called us to a construction site.
Is this the bus?
(The shuttle bus for the Rainbow Club members)
Booking a shuttle bus cost money too.
When we got there, we weren't at a gym.
You just told us to wear a white outfit.
- Right. - We didn't know what was happening.
- I told you to wear a white outfit. - Yes.
There's a reason for that.
(Kian84, dressed in white, gets on the bus for now.)
No one's here yet.
- I was the first one. - You got there quite early.
(He goes all the way to the back as if it was pulling him in.)
(Plopping down)
(Yawning)
Why are we meeting up so early?
Weren't we supposed to meet at 7am?
Right. It was way too early.
How many people are coming?
Two, four, six, eight, ten.
There are 16 seats.
(There's no way 16 people are joining us.)
Oh, hey.
- That's Ji Hyeon's voice. - Hello.
(Ji Hyeon cheerfully walks over.)
My gosh.
- It's been a while. - Hey, it's been a while.
- Why are your hands so chapped? - They're always chapped.
- Have you been well? - Yes.
I've been well. What about you?
I've been well too.
Did you have a nice holiday?
Ji Hyeon is getting friendlier.
By the way, both of us are dressed in white.
Don't we just look like students?
(You're right.)
(A woman dressed in white arrives next.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Nice to meet you.
- That's Dae Ho's other half. - Hello.
(Joking)
- Where would you like to sit? - Hello.
- Sit wherever you want. - Okay.
Since I'm here early, I'll sit in the back too.
Okay.
- Is it your first time meeting her? - Yes.
- It is. - It's our first time, right?
- Aren't you from Mokpo? - Right.
- I'm from Suncheon. - Really?
Yes. Hello. I watched your episodes.
- They hadn't met before that day. - Oh, right.
I bet that was the case for a lot of people.
Is Dae Ho not joining us today?
Is he?
Well, you're close to him. You must know.
- How? We don't stay in touch. - You don't?
- But I think he'll come. - I think he'll come.
(Giggling)
But it's raining today. How will this go?
We were so worried about that. It rained a lot.
A long time ago, even when it rained...
- on a field day like this, - Yes.
people still went through with it, right?
- On our show? - Yes.
No, I mean when you were in school.
- We did even if it rained. - We did even if it rained.
We still went through with it.
We still did it even when it rained.
(It looks like someone has just left his school.)
- My gosh. - Gosh. An after-school program...
- Gosh. No. It's Ju Seung. - My gosh, what's wrong with him?
(Ju Seung shows up in a white taekwondo uniform.)
Where is it?
Wait. That must be it.
Someone's coming.
(Someone else is coming.)
It's Ju Seung.
(He's wearing a taekwondo uniform.)
He's indeed a martial artist.
But you have to understand...
that was probably the only white outfit he had.
- Is that so? - He wears that around his area.
He looked like an elementary school kid.
He could get on the yellow school bus.
Right. The one behind our bus.
- He looks young too. - Right.
- Hello. - Hello. Nice to meet you.
(Intrigued)
Gosh, I ought to make a bold impression.
What bold impression?
You're indeed a martial artist.
I wore this to earn your trust.
(I wore this to earn your trust.)
Is that the bus?
- They're here. - That's it. "Fall Field Day."
The besties are here.
Wait. How many people are joining us?
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- You're here. - Hello.
He's the only one who's excited.
- You're here. - You were the first one?
I was the first one.
My gosh.
I haven't woken up this early in a while.
You should try waking up early in the morning.
I can't.
Mr. Jun. Is he not coming?
- I thought you'd be the first one. - Yes.
(About an hour ago)
My gosh. It's nice and scenic.
- It's nice and scenic, right? - Yes.
I'm glad it's not so sunny. A rainy day isn't so bad.
Given the amount of rainfall,
- it won't be hot today. - It's perfect.
It looks like I'll go shirtless today.
My eyes will be traumatized.
My eyes will be traumatized again.
(Hyun Moo gets out of the car as they bicker.)
- You got there before us. - Of course.
- My gosh. Opening the door... - Hey. Why aren't you getting out?
My gosh, this is nice.
- What's that? - It's raining, Hyun Moo.
I'm the one with the hair loss problem.
- You got one only for yourself? - I should watch out for hair loss.
Come on. Seriously.
What is this? Did you prepare all this?
- I prepared all this. - Gosh.
- You're amazing. - You prepared a lot of stuff.
Hyun Moo prepared all that.
- Let's move the ice box first. - Sure.
My gosh. It's so heavy.
- You set up before we got there. - Gosh.
- Yes. - My goodness.
You have to give me a penalty for this.
A penalty is a bad thing.
Is that a bad thing? Anyway...
Why is it so heavy? I...
It looks like you'll use this as an excuse if you lose.
- No. - You'll use this as an excuse.
Gosh, this is nice.
(Anyway, Hyun Moo, this place is great.)
(It is, right?)
After elementary and middle schools...
- Breathe in the morning air. - It's been a while...
since I felt the rain after I graduated.
- That was a pretty big field. - My gosh. How nice.
- This is great. I'm warming up. - My gosh.
I guess the tracks make me feel alive.
- Really? I'll look forward to it. - Yes.
- You can't make excuses today. - You know what?
It feels right to be walking here.
I hired an agency to set this up.
- My gosh, Hyun Moo. - They set this up...
- President Jun. - last night.
- I hired an agency for this. - There.
They set this up the night before.
They set up everything.
You're indeed President Jun.
You go all out when you do something.
Of course.
- We have to install this. - Really?
It's starting to look legit now.
That's the banner. We need that for the field day.
Today must go well for us to have another field day in the future.
- This is the first one. - Hyun Moo.
- I'm sure... - There.
"Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day."
Gosh, this is amazing.
We joked about this, but it came true.
Gosh, I got goosebumps.
It's because it's chilly here.
Let's hang it there. Around here.
- There? Okay. - It's the perfect spot.
- It's perfect. - Give it some tension.
Tie it up.
You're good.
Okay. It's done.
Be careful.
- You're good. - You think so?
That's it. You're doing a great job.
Just like that.
- Sung Hwan did all the work. - Right. He and I...
- Right. - are rivals.
He kept bossing me around.
There you go. Excellent.
It looks amazing.
It looks like there's a long history.
- This is great, Hyun Moo. - Yes.
- Hyun Moo. Listen. - Like it's got some heritage.
- We're starting a new tradition. - That's right.
- That's cool. - The first field day.
- I rented a loudspeaker. - Nice, Hyun Moo.
A professional loudspeaker was way too expensive.
- Gosh. Given your case, - I just...
this is quite disappointing.
You mean scale, not case.
Hyun Moo. Just read between the lines.
Don't you know me?
- Gosh. - Yes, this one is expensive too.
- Gosh. Check out the scale of this. - Okay.
(I think we're about ready for the field day.)
All done.
The two of the oldest members set up the event.
- That's the thing about field days. - Right. It's different with ours.
They are harder on the teachers...
- than the students. - Of course.
But two principals came out to set this up.
- A principal and a vice-principal. - A vice-principal.
- We took care of that. - A principal and a vice-principal.
- We're done. - We're done.
Then...
- We can just wait for them to come. - We just wait.
They're coming, right?
Hey. If they don't show up,
we... What are we going to do?
We should just run for a bit and go.
We were worried...
- that you might not come. - Right. It was way too quiet.
We actually considered that.
(You punks)
Hyun Moo, it's raining a lot.
Why aren't they here already? It's making me anxious.
What if Ju Seung is the only one who shows up?
- Why aren't they here already? - What's taking them so long?
Is MINHO scared?
(Meanwhile, someone arrives at the bus.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- You're here. - Hello.
- There you are. - Hello.
My gosh, hello.
My gosh, we all look so white.
- Hello. - Hello.
I'm nervous.
- It's Lee Jung. - Lee Jung.
Lee Jung who said I looked older than my age.
- It's my first field day. - Exactly.
It was her first field day ever.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I was quite excited on the bus. - Hello.
People kept coming in.
What?
- Hello. - What's wrong with your hair?
- Hello. - Hi.
You look like a street fighter.
- Your hair... - You do look sharp.
- Like you'll resist the wind. - You sound pretty tough...
in the taekwondo uniform.
You...
(Eating the Shine Muscat)
(Tapping)
Gosh, can I have some?
Thank you.
- I loved that she brought snacks. - Thank you.
It must've been fun on the bus.
Sharing food like that is nice.
Right. That must've been fun.
- You didn't have breakfast, right? - Shine Muscat.
No.
The only thing I got was criticism.
(Joking)
- Do you want the black goat tonic? - Yes. Sounds good.
- You can actually drink this? - I don't know what this is.
- So what's this? - It's the black goat tonic.
- People eat black goats? - Yes.
Really?
- Will this boost my energy? - It looks like a school trip.
It works for me.
- Do you want it? Have it later. - Really?
- Thank you. - It's a precious tonic.
(Gulping down)
I needed to drink that up to boost my energy.
You thoroughly prepared for the field day.
That's great. She does things properly.
Is it good? How does it taste?
- It tastes like a black goat. - It does?
- I guess CODE KUNST isn't coming. - Why isn't CODE KUNST...
- Right. - I don't see CODE KUNST.
Why isn't he here?
- I'm late. - There's always a late student.
You must be punctual.
What? Which bus is it?
There he is.
(I'm sorry I'm late.)
- He's wearing shorts. - He must be so cold!
You're not going to be cold?
Gosh, the bus was full.
President Jun and Sung Hwan are already at the site.
- I see. They're already there. - We can get going now.
- Really? So they weren't late. - All right.
Sir.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Gosh, this bus is packed.
- There are so many people. - We were all excited.
It's been a while since we had a field day.
The weather was a bit gloomy, but we were all excited...
- I was excited too. - because we were together.
I'm sure they prepared a lot of stuff for today.
We're going pretty far.
The road isn't paved at all.
Gosh, this looks like a tough ride.
(Bumpy)
Hey, how come the bus is going...
- Where are we going? - to a remote place?
(Heading over to a mysterious site)
We had been on the road for a while,
- but we couldn't see the field. - We couldn't. Look.
You're right.
Where on earth are we?
- You guys look like a cult group. - Right, sort of.
You were all dressed in white.
Usually, those excited characters...
- end up dying first. - Right.
That's a great theme...
- for OTT shows. - Right.
("Innocent Moo-Ku Field Day")
Why am I seeing barbed-wire fences?
- What? - Wait.
Everyone is terrified.
- Right. - It was scary.
Gosh, we're here!
Wait, look. They're doing something.
- What are they doing? - Look.
- What are they doing? - What?
(They look like tiny dots in the air.)
- It's raining a lot. - It's raining.
Take it.
Let's go!
(It's pouring.)
(It's raining like cats and dogs.)
Come on.
This is like the opening event...
of a slow pork backbone stew restaurant.
Welcome! We've got pork backbone stew!
Hello.
(The bus pulls in from afar.)
(They don't spare their body to welcome the group.)
When I perform in the countryside,
I see a lot of old people dancing like them.
(Fascinated)
What are they doing?
- Welcome. - Welcome!
We wanted to get the party started before you arrived.
We danced for 30 minutes.
For 30 minutes?
- No wonder why you were tired. - Exactly.
We turned on the music and danced for you guys.
- We were confused, though. - The music?
- We were so far away. - We couldn't hear the music at all.
So you didn't hear the music on the bus?
We couldn't hear the music.
- We were confused. - We thought, "What are they doing?"
We maxed out the volume. But you couldn't hear anything.
See? It was quiet.
The First... What does it say over there?
Moo-Ku...
(Flapping)
We were wondering what you were doing when we got off.
From afar, we look like crazy weirdos.
(Suspicious men in the rain)
They're over there.
What are they doing over there?
They're dancing.
What's this?
Welcome.
- Come on. - They're surely trying hard.
They look like the drunk guys you'd see...
- in the neighborhood. - Right.
(Panting)
They used up all of their energy.
It's okay. We had fun.
What crosses your mind...
- when you see that kind of dance? - Come on.
You'll pass out at noon if you keep that up.
You'll get tired early.
(The organizers are brimming with enthusiasm.)
- Okay. Ja Yeon. - Hello.
- That's a big group indeed. - Hello.
Park Ji Hyeon!
Where should we put our bags?
Over here.
Gosh, I know you're busy. But thanks for coming.
Thank you for having me.
You lost weight.
- You think so? - Yes.
But you gained weight.
(Joking)
It felt like going to an uncle's house.
Right. Hadn't it been a while since we all got together?
Right.
It was the first time we had this many people.
- It was the 1st time. - It was the 1st time. Right.
- The 1st time in 10 years. - We usually met in small groups.
- It's suddenly not raining anymore. - It stopped raining.
It stopped raining as soon as you guys arrived.
It rained a lot...
- when we were setting up. - Right.
No one except for MINHO seems excited.
MINHO looks like the Joker. He keeps smiling.
It's called the Innocent Moo-Ku Field Day.
So we'll divide into Teams Moo and Ku. Okay?
I'll join Team MINHO.
- Me too. - I'll join Team MINHO.
- Me too. - Me too.
- I'll join Team MINHO. - Me too.
I'll join Team MINHO too.
(Captain Ku will join Team MINHO too.)
- You don't know what we're playing. - No.
(Pulling in)
- What's going on? - What?
What is that?
- What's going on? - What is this?
Ko Kang Yong is here.
What?
- For real? - Really?
- This is crazy. - Hey.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - He came in a suit.
- He's an MBC employee. - He's got a name tag too.
- A fancy announcer for our event. - Nice to see you.
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
- On behalf of MBC, - Yes.
I brought presents.
The CEO of MBC is personally providing you with these presents.
Everyone, let's give it up for him!
He knows how to run a party.
I should work hard today. There are home appliances!
Everyone, look over there.
There's an ambulance on standby.
- We got a bigger one than idols. - Exactly.
- We're much older than them. - Of course.
All right. Let's move the prizes Kang Yong brought.
(Swarming over to move the prizes)
Gosh, what's this?
My goodness! These are home appliances!
- These are home appliance boxes! - Gosh.
Seeing fancy prizes definitely got us excited.
- Lame prizes can't motivate us. - Exactly.
- Right. - Yes.
Let's stack them up neatly here.
My gosh. This is amazing.
- A Dyson? - It's a Dyson?
Of course. We ought to use tools.
Give them to me. Come down and help us here.
Let's go.
- Look how strong he is. - Put the rice sacks on the cart.
Just put the sacks on the cart!
We've got a cart!
- He could ruin his shoulders. - I should do lunges.
Look. He's doing squats too.
- I told him to put them on a cart. - I mean, lunges.
- My gosh. - There he goes again.
In case it ruins your outfit.
- Why is he wasting his energy? - Why?
This is how people give out their holiday presents.
Really?
- President Jun. - Yes.
Okay, I got it. I'll introduce them. Give me a second.
This is mine.
- You should get a haircut. - Kang Yong prepared everything...
for our event. Thank you. How do I put this on?
- What's that? - What is it?
- They don't listen. - Is he going to sing?
This will be a long event.
- Protect your voice. - There are numbers on it.
There were so many people.
Our teachers used to call out, "Attention."
- I could understand why. - Right.
You guys didn't listen to me at all.
This is great. Now, we're talking. This hits the spot.
Okay. From now on, I'm going to explain some things.
- What? - We don't want to buy pearl cream.
I don't want to buy latex mattresses.
- We don't want to buy gemstones. - No.
All right. I'll introduce the prizes for the winning team.
All the prizes are sponsored by the CEO of MBC, Ahn Hyung Joon.
- CEO Ahn. - Yes.
CEO Ahn.
- Thank you. - You'll see them in the front.
The most popular hair styling device and home appliance...
will be awarded to an MVP.
Yes! They're mine.
- Really? - A hair styling device...
- My gosh. - A hair styling device...
Woo Il.
Woo Il is excited for real.
- Great. - An air purifier...
and a vacuum cleaner will go to the same person.
- They're mine! - To the MVP.
The prizes were much better than I expected.
There's a prize for the winning team.
Look behind you. Na Rae, you love this.
- Is it meat? - It's Korean beef!
(The Korean beef set)
- Great! - Everyone on the winning team...
will get one.
- Everyone on the winning team! - Give that to me.
(An appetizing color)
Let's grill one now!
- What did you say? - Let's grill one now!
Open your eyes first.
There will be bonus games between our matches.
The prizes for the bonus games...
- are 10kg bags of rice from Yeoju. - Yeoju.
- Rice from Yeoju. - Nice.
- Rice. - The winners will get rice.
To map out how today will go,
I came up with a program.
- All right. Sung Hwan. - Yes.
- Bring the scroll. - The scroll?
What am I, his servant?
- He was like Hyun Moo's servant. - He was obedient.
President Jun prepared this.
Everything must have cost him money.
- Look. - Here's the program.
This isn't a third-rate field day. We have planned everything.
Here's today's program.
One, two, three.
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
These are the events...
- Sung Hwan and I came up with. - Right.
(Impressed)
- A tug of war is the first event? - Move the Flour?
- For the first event, - A special game. A relay race.
we have the opening ceremony.
- There's a relay race. - This looks fun.
- The first game is a tug of war. - A tug of war.
- Next, we have Move the Flour. - Move the Flour.
We won't do it if it rains.
We'll play this game if it doesn't rain.
- Do we have to carry it? - What kind of game is it?
It's mouth-to-mouth.
- Mouth-to-mouth? - What?
- So... - Not to waste any particles.
It might turn into a dough halfway through.
Then it will be a warm dough.
(Warm liquid will be added.)
- A warm dough? - Yes.
Make sujebi with that later.
Gosh, this is annoying.
- Gosh, that's disgusting. - That's disgusting.
- Mouth-to-mouth... - At the end,
it will turn into songpyeon.
- Yes! That's spot on. - Yes.
- Chuseok is all about songpyeon. - Move the Flour.
- Chuseok was a long time ago. - Move the Flour.
Then there's a special game.
Look forward to this game. This is the highlight.
- Did you prepare this? - Yes, I did.
You'll be dying to find out.
- Next, we have a group relay race. - That sounds fun.
- Gosh, this is it. - I'm looking forward to this.
- A relay race? - This is...
- It's a relay race. - A relay race.
Relay races are the highlight...
- of field days. - It's the highlight.
- Right. We'll give out... - That's it.
the prizes at the awards and closing ceremonies.
- An awards ceremony? - Yes.
I injured my finger.
- I'll work hard. - Woo Il.
Woo Il. My kneecaps are busted.
Are you a Pomeranian?
Any more questions?
When will we divide into teams?
- Let's divide into teams. - We will now divide into teams.
- Okay. - This is important.
Pairs with similar athletic abilities...
will play rock-paper-scissors.
Losers will line up here. And the winners will line up here.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Losers will be on Team Ku.)
It felt like we were kids again.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(MINHO loses, and Kian84 wins.)
(MINHO joins Team Ku, and Kian84 joins Team Moo.)
(MINHO is on Team Ku. Everyone, make some noise!)
- This is it! - We won!
- We have it in the bag. - We have it in the bag.
- Where... - There's no tension here.
- Could you move back a bit? - I don't know.
- Team Moo, move back. - Okay.
- Team Ku, move back this way. - I see. Great.
- Let's have some space here. - He's so reliable.
Someone's here. It's Dae Ho.
- Who? - Dae Ho is here!
- I really thought he wasn't coming. - Okay!
Dae Ho came here straight...
after he landed in Korea from his trip.
I'm sorry.
- He's here. It's Dae Ho. - Dae Ho is here!
- Okay! - Yes! Hello.
He's here. Wait.
- You have 1 more player. - You have 1 more player.
- Then he could... - I'll play...
when numbers don't match.
Yes. Okay!
I'm feeling competitive now that we're divided into teams.
(Team Ku)
(The ace member, Choi MINHO)
(The man with never-ending super energy)
(The best fighting power of his team)
I was disappointed that we weren't on the same team.
(He's been training only for this day.)
(Ju Seung and Sung Hwan, the bodyweight workout duo)
(KEY, the former waterskier in middle school)
(The man with a golden balance)
(Kim Dae Ho, the flying squirrel on Mount Inwang)
(Ok Ja Yeon, Michael Okdan)
(And there's also Ji Hyeon with acrobatic skills.)
(Team Ku mostly consists of athletes.)
(Team Moo)
(Running is the life for Running84.)
There's a runner.
- Yes. That's it. - Ms. Park Lats.
There's Ms. Park Lats.
- The monkey. - My gosh.
I'm glad you learned parkour.
- Parkour. - There's the monkey.
(There's Lee Jung, a flexible dancer.)
(Jae Hyeon who recently gained muscles)
(Kang Yong runs on Mount Nam.)
(Dugong Jang Woo can swim in the waves of the Black Sea.)
It was so nice.
(To top it off, they've been forming their teamwork for many years.)
(Team Moo will use their bond as a weapon.)
Our team is pretty good too.
- Our team is amazing. - The oldest and the youngest...
- are on our team. - Right.
Our team can show people what life is about.
- Of course. We have a great story. - That's right.
- And my team doesn't? - We've got a great story.
- Our team is pretty good too. - There's...
- something romantic about our team. - There are tears. Of course.
(Which team will come out victorious?)
By the way, we split into two teams of equal strength.
- Right. - His team was powerful too.
Go.
Victory is ours!
- Moomoo Challenge! - Moomoo Challenge!
Why...
- Even if you don't like it... - Listen.
- You didn't even try at all. - Listen.
- Look. - He didn't do that?
- You didn't even try. - But...
- Wait. - Look.
- I couldn't do it at the same time. - Look at him.
This was the difference.
KEY was great at team building activities.
So everyone on our team was so motivated from the get-go.
You guys had a cheer squad.
- Moomoo Challenge! - Moomoo Challenge!
(Shy)
- What is that? - Great.
That made us look so beautifully human.
- Great. - That was great.
- It was predictable and great. - Team Ku.
- Show us. - Yes.
Here it goes. All right. Go.
- MINHO, MINHO, let's go! - MINHO, MINHO, let's go!
That's too much pressure on one person.
- Right. - Of course.
- My gosh. This isn't good. - It's a team match.
- Of course. - They're worshipping him too much.
Worship him?
- No. I worshipped myself that day. - Listen.
The first game is...
- a tug of war. - Okay.
- This will be fun. - We'll win no matter what.
We're doing best 2 out of 3.
Best 2 out of 3? Okay.
- We have to lean back. - We will...
- Will strong ones go to the front? - We must lean back for sure.
We don't even need to cheer. Just lean back. That's it.
Lean back. And our tempo will be off too.
We'll just lean back. They won't have any energy left.
But how did he end up becoming the brain of the team?
- No one knew how to play. - We didn't know.
- We weren't knowledgeable. - I see.
We ended up listening to the ones who stepped up...
- in the beginning. - You went with whoever took charge.
He said, "Lean back as soon as we begin."
He sounded like an expert.
I thought he was the survivor from "Squid Game."
I think he was just a fan of the show.
Right. He sounded so professional. So we had to trust him.
People like him are usually the first ones to die.
We do have a disadvantage with this game.
- Why? - The weight difference is big.
They have an upper hand.
- We had a physical disadvantage. - Lee Jung...
and Na Rae were too light.
Our team had 2 women when their team had only 1.
There's a strategy to this.
When they tug,
it's important to chant our slogan.
Jang Woo, why don't you lead?
- Say, "Let's go." - Jang Woo kept us together.
- He had a philosophy... - That's important.
about the tug of war.
- Let's try pulling it. - Okay.
This will be the tempo.
(They will pull at the same time with the slogan.)
Jang Woo kept us together.
(Glancing)
My gosh. Are we going to have this match tomorrow?
- What are we doing? - The sun will go down.
My gosh.
- This can't be. - Hear me out.
- He's going over the strategy. - Right now...
- Look over there. - My goodness.
- It took so long. - We just started.
- We should put on the gloves. - We need the cotton gloves.
- Should we put them on? - Go get them.
Darn it.
- I naturally obeyed like that. - He's so obedient.
- Their average height is higher. - And they're bigger.
Let's go. We're set.
It's fine as long as we're having fun.
- One should be enough. - Right.
- That looks cool. - "Let's go" might be better.
- The sense of rhythm is important. - Ji Hyeon.
- Okay. - Hold it like this?
- A tug of war? No way. - It doesn't matter.
Na Rae, show them the fruit of your lateral muscles today.
- Okay. - Lean back.
- That's it. - And pull back.
- That was it. Like rowing. - This is why you worked out.
- Row. - He was detailed.
No, not like that. Pretend you're rowing.
All right. Are you ready?
I'll blow the whistle.
- Okay. - Let's grab the rope.
- Grab it. - Grab the rope.
- Gosh, I bet they're strong. - My gosh.
- All right. - Do we start squatting down?
Our slogan is "Let's go."
- Let's do this. - Great.
- In the middle... - Are you ready?
- Let's do this. - My gosh.
But...
Jang Woo looks so reliable.
- Of course. - I remember doing it this way.
(Moving)
- That's... - Wait.
(Come on!)
I was testing the waters.
What was that?
- Listen. - What?
Hey, Jang Woo weighs more than me.
(Pulling)
- Jang Woo! - Come on.
- He weighs more than me. - It was quite heavy.
- They might fight. - Hey, you thug.
- Go ahead. Let's fight. - Hey.
If we can do this on the beat, we'll win.
- Right here. - Wait.
- This one... Pull it. - Pull it.
- Are you ready? - We must begin with the rope down.
- Put it down. - Right.
- Put it down. - Put it down.
- Put it down? - Put it down for now.
Put it down.
- This is hard. - Put it down?
- Dae Ho is disciplining his junior. - What?
- Dae Ho. Aren't I right? - No.
- All right. Spread out. - Don't let him get to you.
- Mister. - Stay there.
- Aren't you just a regular guy? - No.
- That guy... - Hands off.
- You're not even an announcer. - Come on.
- You're not even an announcer. - Look how competitive we are.
- He's not even an announcer now. - He's right.
- Seriously? - He's just a celebrity now.
- Hands off. - Right?
- There's no seniority in games! - Really?
- Hands off. - Gosh.
- We could've just played. Why... - Hands off.
Hands off? We have to grab it right away?
- I'm not going to play. - Okay.
- We are supposed to grab it. - We are supposed to grab it.
- Grab it. - Just grab the rope.
- Grab it. - Grab the rope.
Don't pull it. Just grab it.
- Okay. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Hey, you can't be there.
(Team Ku will lean back the moment they begin.)
(Woo Il leads the team.)
(Team Moo will pull at the same time with the slogan.)
(Jang Woo leads the team.)
Move back.
- Get ready. - All right. Just lean back.
(Their pride is at stake on the first game.)
- Seriously. It was no joke. - It was the first team game.
Honestly, I had no idea how this would pan out.
(Nervous)
I'll join you. Get ready.
(The first match of their field day)
(The match begins.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Right. They took the lead in the beginning.
- See? They took the lead. - They took the lead at first.
(Like planned, Team Moo...)
(pulls the rope at the same time with the slogan.)
(Chanting)
Here it goes! There's the bulldozer.
- They just pulled. - They didn't chant anything.
- We chanted our slogan. - Our teamwork is great.
Our teamwork is great. Look at Jang Woo.
(Pulling as hard as he can)
(Falling down)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- This... - What did you do?
(Chanting)
(Team Ku collapses in an instant.)
- Yes! - This was horrible.
(Dragged)
(Glinting eyes)
(Chanting the slogan infinitely like Jang Woo's strategy)
They were like dried yellow corvinas on a string.
(General Jang Woo didn't stop until the end.)
(Pulling until the end)
(Celebrating)
- Yes! - Yes!
(Passed out)
- What was that? - What?
Here's what's important.
The guy at the head was supposed to hold it together.
When you fell down,
- Everyone fell down. - everyone fell down too.
We had an upper hand...
- in the beginning. - Right.
Once we had the lead and leaned back,
had we pulled at the same time,
- we could have won. - Right.
You guys lost because of Woo Il.
- Woo Il was the spy. - Right.
When I leaned back,
I locked eyes with Woo Il and Dae Ho.
(What is this? What are we going to do?)
(Team Ku was flustered and faced a miserable defeat.)
I thought the three of you were a chunk of something.
- So... - You guys got dragged together.
I said, "Let go." Woo Il said, "Grab it."
"Let go." "Grab it."
- Right. - You need more than strength...
- for that game. - It's about the teamwork.
You need a strategy.
- Hold on. - My gosh.
- Wait. - I didn't even have to pull hard.
- Hold on. You didn't get it. - What is it?
- You can't lean forward. - What?
No, I leaned back the moment we began.
- No, we leaned forward. - Listen.
- You leaned forward. - Hey.
- Why did you lean forward? - We were supposed to lean back.
- I said to lean back. - It's not that.
- But he leaned forward. - They're fighting.
- They're super weak. - Gosh.
They're a mess.
- I didn't even have to pull hard. - The thing is...
Gosh, they're so strong.
All right.
- They're so strong. - We were great.
- Great. I didn't even pull hard. - This is fun.
- I didn't even pull hard. - It was fun when we were winning.
- Right. - Jang Woo.
- Our tempo was great. - Yes, it was great.
- It was great. - It was all you.
- Jang Woo is good at this. - You were great.
He's good.
Let's end this.
- Hey, what was that? - Listen.
- I fell. - In the beginning...
- Right. You... - It's because I fell.
- This was what happened. - We should move back.
- They kept criticizing each other. - Listen.
- Come on. - You can't slip this time.
- Not again. - I won't.
- He lost his balance. - Then we should switch places.
- I kept slipping to the back. - I'll take the second spot.
Hold on. I should just...
- No, don't take them off. - No.
Are they slippery?
- This is fun. - We'll win if we win this round.
- We can totally win this. - Yes.
Sung Hwan took off his shoes, but he shouldn't do that.
- He took off his shoes? - Yes.
- Sung Hwan is the weak link. - He commented on it right away.
Why did you take off your shoes?
My shoes are like ballet shoes.
- What are you talking about? - So...
- They are so slippery like this. - They're sneakers.
I wear them often too. But they aren't slippery.
To make it fair, we'll let you guys...
- blow the whistle this time. - Yes. For this time.
- Okay? - Okay.
Okay.
Shift your weight backward.
- Tug the rope on the beat. - Let's go.
Our tempo is important.
- Get ready to lean back. - Gosh, everyone looks so serious.
- We were so serious. - Not yet.
Hey, go to the back now.
(Their rivalry is intense.)
Come on!
- That hurts. - Get ready.
- Yes. Grab it. - We got this.
- Let's go. - We got this.
Get ready.
- Get ready. - Get ready to lean back.
(Which team will come out victorious?)
(The second round begins.)
- Lean back. - Let's go.
(They try to hold out.)
They always take the lead at first.
We're always behind at first.
- But we turned the tables here. - Lean back.
(General Jang Woo gains momentum with the slogan.)
(Shouting)
(Lean back!)
- What's he doing? - Hey!
- Hey, Woo Il is the weak link. - What's he doing?
- We can't fall back. - Let's go.
What?
- We can't fall back. - See? He fell too.
(Don't fall back!)
- Seriously. They're so bad at this. - We turned the tables then.
(General Jang Woo pulls harder when he sees them on the grass.)
This isn't right.
- Come on. - Pull.
What's this?
(Heave-ho)
(Collapsing)
No way.
(Team Ku gets thrown to the ground.)
(Cheering)
Hyun Moo is so happy.
He even did a ceremony.
He was so annoying.
(Did we win because my pelvis didn't stop?)
(He pretends not to see Hyun Moo.)
- Everyone was so close together. - I mean...
- Well done. - It was too...
- He knew what to do. - He used a lot of energy.
- Jang Woo, thank you. - My goodness.
- Jang Woo was something else. - Jang Woo, well done.
Jang Woo sure is different.
- He's the best. - He's heavy.
- I bet they were startled. - It was fun.
We had the weight and wits.
Why did you lie down?
We need to pull at the same time.
They went, "Heave-ho."
- They lost because of him. - Why was the ground slippery?
The first event was tug of war.
Team Moo won.
They did well.
We did really well.
- Okay. - All right.
- The next game. - The next game.
(Pulling up)
That's how you do it.
(Solemn)
(He ties his hair in order to win.)
Tonghak Peasant Revolution.
He's preparing to go to war.
(Fascinated)
Now comes the event you're looking forward to.
It's the Mouth-to-Mouth Move the Flour.
- Mouth-to-Mouth. - It's a controversial game.
Since the game involves flour, we'll do it...
- over a plastic sheet on the track. - Okay.
We'll spill flour.
(They take the rope and go to the track again.)
It's nice to exercise on a rainy day.
- It's nice. - It's nice, right?
- Yes. - It's nice.
Suddenly, I got a dopamine rush.
- Where is the plastic sheet? - It's here.
Let's lay a plastic sheet.
We might spill flour.
Gosh, Woo Il.
- He's a good worker. - I know.
- A farmer sure is different. - I know.
Here. Let's cut it here.
Keep going.
- We're set. - Yes.
It's nice to have a lot of people.
We did all the work in the morning.
(This is nice.)
- Where should I move it? - Move it to the middle.
- The middle. - The middle. Tear it.
- Kang Yong is good. - Cut it in half.
In half.
Kang Yong was like a passionate principal.
How does the game go?
Please explain the rules.
That's right. How do we play the game?
- All the teammates will stand here. - Okay.
One member will scoop up flour with the shovel in his or her mouth.
(Scoop up flour with the shovel in the mouth.)
- Everyone will have a shovel. - With a shovel.
- Move it. - That's right.
- Move it. - From a shovel to a shovel.
The last person will receive the flour and put it in a bowl.
The team with more weight will win.
- Okay. - Okay.
A game like this one is fun.
That's right. It should be a fun field day.
The time limit is 90 seconds.
That's so long.
- Will there be one round? - One round.
It has to be a one-round match.
It'll be bad if there are two rounds.
- This is funny. - No.
- Don't laugh. - This is funny.
- Don't laugh. - No.
I'm the one who's the most at risk.
- He... - Don't laugh.
- Don't laugh. - Suppress it.
(Laughing)
It's really funny.
We need to do a good job of deciding on the order.
- The order. - When we do this,
wouldn't it be better to go from high to low?
- It'll be better. - Right?
Comparing to going up...
Spread out.
- We stood in the order of height. - Yes.
You have 90 seconds.
- Get ready. - It'll begin now.
(Team Moo's first victory was electrifying.)
Get ready.
(We'll win this time as well!)
Get ready. Set...
(For Move the Flour, Team Moo goes first.)
(The match begins.)
He scooped it really well.
- Hey. - What's that?
(Delivering to the next person)
He's like an excavator.
Hey.
(Laughing)
Jang Woo did that.
For goodness' sake.
(He burst out laughing!)
No, have a sad thought!
(Let's have a sad thought.)
My goodness.
(Shaking)
Why is he shaking his head?
Kang Yong should've dropped it, but he couldn't do it well.
(Stay still. I'll help you.)
(Shocked)
Please!
- What? - Hey.
- This game... - We need to win.
(The amount of flour diminishes as it gets moved.)
It reached the end.
I didn't get as much as I expected.
Thirty seconds have passed.
(The 1st scoop gets delivered in 30 seconds.)
It reached the end.
- So much of it entered my nose! - What's wrong with him?
Jang Woo wanted to eat!
- What is he doing? - What is he doing?
Why...
- What's going on? - Come on.
They're ruined.
They're seriously ruined.
What's that?
I needed to shake it off.
You should've used your brain.
Stop laughing!
(I can't help it.)
(Laughing)
Everyone is laughing.
It's no wonder I'm not getting any flour.
How am I supposed to do this?
There you go.
(We're the winners for laughing until the end.)
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
- four, three, - What?
- two, one. - What's wrong with him?
- Time's up. - What was that?
- Let it slide. - Okay.
- That counts. - I added it as I heard the whistle.
- Jang Woo. - I told you to have sad thoughts!
- It was a buzzer-beater. - Why did you keep laughing?
- The 3rd and 4th ones did badly. - I mean...
My nose...
What's up with that face?
He looks like a badger.
Kian84, why did you shake?
The flour wouldn't slide down.
You did this.
That game was fun.
- Did I dust off the flour? - Most of it is gone.
- It's all over your face. - Really?
- It's all over your face. - Where?
(Dusting off)
Let's decide on the order.
I'll stand next to Woo Il.
For us, it wasn't a festival.
Since we had lost in the first round,
we totally saw it as a competition.
Ji Hyeon, can you hold in your laughter?
I can do it.
- I'll do it. - In that case...
Can you suppress your laughter?
(Ji Hyeon, will you be okay?)
Gosh, they had it hard.
I can't hold in my laughter.
If you do that, I can't hold it in.
I really can't hold it in.
Since I can hold it in, I'll pass the flour to Woo Il.
I'll stand next to Woo Il.
Funny faces don't make me laugh.
Two people with a poker face stood next to Woo Il.
- All right. Are you ready? - Let's do a cheer.
- Let's do a cheer. - All right.
- Set, go. - Set, go.
- MINHO, MINHO, let's go! - MINHO, MINHO, let's go!
- That's the spirit. - That's idolatry.
They're wasting their energy.
Are you ready?
Gosh, that's...
- Hold on. What's this? - What?
- Young man, you can't do that. - It's okay.
- It needs to be flat. - No.
- You can't do that. - Come on.
- Come on. - Come on.
Ms. Mount Mudeung, be quiet.
You can't create a slope ahead of time.
- You can't do that. - It should be flat.
- It should be flat. - You guys should have a fight.
- Shall we do that next? - Seriously.
- MMA. - It'll be the next event.
MMA.
Jae Hyeon had piled it up...
- like a mountain earlier. - No, he didn't.
- Come on. - Come on.
- Come on. - What?
Let's begin.
- Let's go. - Let's do this with sincerity.
Get ready. Set...
Woo Il will make people laugh.
That's right. Peasant Revolution will make people laugh.
(Team Ku scoops up flour for the first time.)
Peasant Revolution will make people laugh.
(Please don't laugh.)
- He didn't laugh. - Funny faces don't make me laugh.
Tonghak Peasant Revolution.
She'll burst out laughing.
She didn't even look at him.
- It was a good strategy. - I see.
- It was a good strategy. - She didn't even look at him.
- She didn't look. - He'll burst out laughing.
Dae Ho!
He's laughing!
- He's laughing! - Dae Ho.
- What's up with him? - Oh, my.
- You know... - He must like her for real.
- He was excited to get it from her. - He must be insane.
- What's wrong with him? - Ja Yeon delivered it.
- Oh, my. - He was excited...
since she was close.
Was he serious when we had Code Name: Mother Nature?
- He was serious. - He was serious.
(He stayed next to her all day long.)
(His love for her blossomed secretly.)
(I was seriously happy.)
(Now, she's right in front of him.)
Good.
- Dae Ho's face is red. - Oh, my.
- Look at that. - Oh, my.
My goodness.
- He's excited. - What's wrong with him?
Why are you filming a dating show here?
He's waiting.
He's so funny.
(I'm waiting.)
He's excited.
He loves it.
Only Dae Ho is excited right now.
Ja Yeon is focused on the task.
Look at Dae Ho.
- What's wrong with him? - Dae Ho, your hands.
- He's laughing. - He can't hide his love.
If he likes her that much, he should confess his love.
In the middle of Myeongdong.
"Do you want to be my woman?"
Dae Ho!
(He can only cough up flour.)
He's laughing.
Why did he stand there?
- Gosh, he stood next to Ja Yeon. - There you go.
The two of them are really good.
His face...
- Let's watch Sung Hwan. - Your hands.
- He loves it. - Sung Hwan.
- They're good. - They're good.
Ten seconds. Ten, nine,
eight, seven, six,
- Dae Ho, why is your face red? - five, four,
three, two, one.
Time's up.
- Okay. - Who laughed?
- Good. - We have enough.
Who spilled the flour?
Nice. We moved a lot of flour.
- Dae Ho... - What's wrong with you?
- Dae Ho... - He's filming a dating show.
- That's right. - Dae Ho spilled half of it.
- His face turned red. - We'll win.
- This is ours. - Let's see.
But...
It was a landslide victory.
- We laughed too much. - The event was Move the Flour.
- It's too bad. - Team Ku won.
(In Move the Flour, Team Ku won.)
- Yes. - Okay.
- Well done. - MINHO, MINHO, let's go!
- Team Ku. - Well done.
Let's do better.
MINHO is the best.
(We can't lose when it comes to cheers.)
(Spinning)
- When did you guys do that? - What a beautiful sight.
Seriously. It's no joke.
The current score is 1 to 1. It's a tie.
- Okay. - It's 1 to 1.
It's good. It's neck-and-neck.
Was that game scored the same way as the tug of war?
- Of course. - It was a main game.
I see that it was an important game.
- It was an official event. - One point.
- It's raining. - It's raining.
Hey, it's raining.
- It's raining so suddenly. - It fell after the flour game.
- I know. It began right after. - Right after.
Let's hurry up and clean up.
- Let's clean up. - Let's do this.
Only Kang Yong is exercising in a suit.
(Kian84 dusts off Kang Yong's suit.)
Oh, my.
- He'll need a new suit. - He'll need a new suit.
I'll give you money for dry cleaning.
- Not a new suit? - Don't you have workout clothes?
You'll just give him money for dry cleaning.
- Not a new suit? - He's sharp.
You're so pathetic.
You could buy your junior a new suit.
- Jae Hyeon is very sharp. - Yes.
He's sharp.
It suddenly rained a lot.
All right.
Now, everyone,
we'll have an individual match.
What's the prize?
- The prize is rice. - Yes.
(I'll get ready.)
We'll use this time...
- for a special match. - Okay.
(Special game)
All right.
- The match everyone wants to see. - What?
How embarrassing.
- Could it be... - What is it?
It's a big match that's highly anticipated.
Let's begin the 100m sprint between Hyun Moo and Sung Hwan.
(Hyun Moo versus Sung Hwan, 100m sprint)
- The 100m sprint? - My goodness.
It's a rematch.
(The revenge match puts their pride on the line.)
That's right.
It was a revenge match for you.
I was a bit excited about this one.
Go!
Because of that...
We've watched this so many times.
(They had a 100m sprint at the MBC Square.)
We ran so diligently.
(Hyun Moo easily passed Sung Hwan and won!)
I got a cramp in my legs.
(I got a cramp in my legs.)
That was how the field day began.
- Yes. - That's right.
You can't come up with an excuse because that's the official track.
- That's right. - Yes.
I took good care of my body for that day.
He talks the most.
The track should be a bit long for the match.
It should be this long.
There are groups.
The winner of each group will advance to the final.
And the final winner will win 20kg of rice.
You know, I'm curious about my record.
- Same here. I want to run. - I've never done it.
- The 3 of us should run. - The 3 of us?
That's right. Lee Jung hasn't done it.
She never had an opportunity.
I need to warm up my body.
I bet Ja Yeon can run well.
I don't know if I can run well or not.
I bet she can run well.
Hey, this is a big match.
- Look at that. - He's acting out again.
He's wearing ballet shoes.
He's a ballerino.
(Annoyed)
(Hurried)
Gosh, are you race walking?
He has a good start.
I'm usually fast.
That time, I had a cramp in my legs.
- Kang Yong. - You weren't that fast.
- Kang Yong, I'm not lying. - Really?
I couldn't pick up the speed because I had a cramp in my legs.
I... How do I explain myself?
This is a revenge match for you.
You'll run in a proper setting.
- Okay. But today... - If you do badly today,
- you have no excuse. - I won't give any excuses.
But I did get a cramp that time.
You won't get a cramp today.
I don't know.
Why do you get a cramp every day?
(Hyun Moo doesn't understand.)
- I get a cramp every day. - Well,
he unbuttoned his shorts for this.
He gets a cramp all the time.
Sung Hwan, good luck.
- There they go. - Sung Hwan, let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Sung Hwan, let's go. - Let's go.
Jun Hyun Moo!
Get ready. Set...
- It's raining. - It's raining a lot.
Gosh, it's like a drama.
Set...
(Hurried)
- A false start. My goodness. - My goodness.
My body leaned forward since I had a big torso.
For goodness' sake.
- That was a false start. - Get ready. Set...
(Go!)
- That's fast. - My goodness.
(They run at full speed.)
- Go! - My goodness.
They're neck-and-neck.
(It's a close match and neither one wants to lose.)
(They're neck-and-neck.)
Come on!
Hyun Moo, a bit more.
(It's a great match where the runners are equally matched.)
(Victory is mine.)
It's like "Nowhere to Hide."
(Not on my watch.)
He's running with gritted teeth.
(I'll bet my everything on this moment.)
(Victory is close.)
Hyun Moo, a bit more.
(Who will laugh in the end?)
- A bit more. - He got ahead.
(Hyun Moo gets ahead toward the end.)
Hyun Moo.
(Grinning)
That match was the most entertaining.
(Moomoo won!)
It was unexpected.
Hyun Moo is fast.
I'm good at sprinting.
He got ahead.
Really?
Moomoo won!
I got a cramp.
You got a cramp again!
- Okay. I admit defeat. - He had...
He had a nice start.
- Hyun Moo. - You did better than better.
I didn't run fast because I was scared.
I let Hyun Moo win.
- "I let Hyun Moo win." - I lost.
He should just admit defeat.
- I know. It's nothing. - It's a matter of pride.
I lost due to the difference of two perilla leaves' width.
Just how thick are those perilla leaves?
Moomoo, you're very fast.
- I'm fast, right? - Yes, you're very fast.
Your body is light.
- That's right. My feet are fast. - He's fast.
- Hyun Moo. - He's full of surprises.
- You were so fast. - Hyun Moo, not bad.
You're bad.
- All right. - Why are you panting so much?
The special match between Hyun Moo and Sung Hwan.
- It's official. - It's official.
- Seriously. - Hyun Moo won.
(Jun Hyun Moo won!)
No more excuses.
- That's right. Hyun Moo is good. - Yes.
You admit defeat, right?
- I admit defeat. - Okay.
He's fast.
Group One, Lee Ju Seung, Park Ji Hyeon,
Im Woo Il, and Ahn Jae Hyeon.
How were people divided into these groups?
Hyun Moo and I did it the day before.
We considered the records.
All right.
On your mark.
Set...
(Go!)
(He picks up the speed as soon as the race begins.)
(Surprised)
- Ji Hyeon is fast. - Ji Hyeon is fast.
(Screaming)
(I refuse to lose.)
(Another man refuses to lose.)
Jae Hyeon surprised me.
(Who will come in 1st and become happy?)
Ji Hyeon is fast.
- Look. - Look at Jae Hyeon.
What?
(Runners are equally matched in Group 1.)
(Ji Hyeon, Jae Hyeon)
(It's hard to predict the result of such a close match.)
(Who will be the winner?)
(Ji Hyeon was one step ahead.)
(Ji Hyeon placed 1st with incredible speed.)
He's fast.
- Look at him. - Woo Il.
(I'm so exhausted.)
- He's fast. - Ji Hyeon can run very well.
- What? - I placed second.
Woo Il, you did badly.
From Group One,
- Ji Hyeon advanced to the final. - Yes.
Ji Hyeon is very fast.
Will only the first place advance?
- He ran very fast. - I placed third.
Ji Hyeon had explosive speed.
He can run well.
Group Two, Ok Ja Yeon, Lee Jung, and Park Na Rae.
It's the women's group.
Set...
(Lee Jung takes the lead.)
Lee Jung.
She's fast.
(Doing her best)
- Okay. - Come on.
- How cute. - I nearly died.
(Grimacing)
- Na Rae! - Na Rae is like a baby.
- Ok Ja Yeon! - You never know.
(Ja Yeon gets ahead in the end.)
You never know.
- Ok Ja Yeon won! - Okay.
(Ja Yeon places 1st in Group 2 by a small margin.)
My goodness.
She can run really well.
Gosh, how are they so fast?
Ja Yeon placed first.
You can run really well.
I did my best.
- She came from behind and won. - Seriously.
(Group 2 members are happy regardless of the result.)
She was so scary.
Group Three, Lee Jang Woo, KEY, Jun Hyun Moo, and Ku Sung Hwan.
He can run with his eyes closed.
(I'm exhausted already.)
It'll be a big match between Jang Woo and Sung Hwan.
You'll win.
Bring it forward a bit.
Set...
(Go!)
- Why is he looking at the side? - He's looking at me.
Why do you keep looking?
- They're fast. - My goodness.
(Neck-and-neck)
(Jang Woo picks up the speed.)
(I still have my running skills.)
(Jang Woo shows his talent after tug of war.)
(Jang Woo places 1st in Group 3 after the last spurt!)
(The result surprises everyone.)
- What happened? - Jang Woo!
- Jang Woo placed 1st. - Jang Woo placed 1st.
- What was that? - That's who I am!
I was so surprised. He's very fast.
This group is funny.
Their hands move busily, but they aren't that fast.
Exactly.
And at a glance, it looks like...
- they're running in a line. - I know.
While they're fast...
We shouldn't judge Jang Woo by what we see now.
- That's right. - He ran and exercised a lot...
- back in the day, - That's right.
- That's right. - He has a nice body.
He remembers how to run.
The last one is a big match.
CODE KUNST, Kim Dae Ho, MINHO, and Kian84.
It's one of the main matches.
They're runners.
This is the match of professionals.
(He has agility from doing parkour.)
I've never done short-distance running.
(He has no confidence.)
Maybe I'll place last.
(He calls himself Mount Inwang's flying squirrel.)
Kian84, you're the pride of runners.
- A professional runner. - The genre is different.
(The pride of Korean runners who ruled New York)
Kian84 has pride.
He steels his heart when it's necessary.
(He's ready to go.)
- Let's go. - All right.
(Hold on a second.)
(Rummaging)
What? He's taking something out.
I'll change into my running shoes.
- He's using equipment. - Come on.
Did he change into his running shoes?
(Jumping)
- His body is light. - He's using equipment.
We have MINHO in this group.
(He has strong legs from running up the mountain.)
Why is he like that?
We didn't run against human.
- He isn't human. - He's a machine.
(His passion burns brightly whenever he exercises.)
There's madness in his eyes.
He's an ironman.
- We have MINHO in this group. - Gosh.
Why did you add a runner who isn't human?
He changed into new shoes.
(Group 4 of the netherworld lines up before the starting line.)
We'll begin right away. On your mark.
Set...
- Set... - MINHO is fast.
(MINHO's start is unrivaled.)
Look at him go.
He's fast.
- Look at MINHO. - Hey.
What? It's a monkey!
It's a monkey!
What? Just now...
- Oh, my. - Saru.
- Saru. - Saru.
Saru.
(I love Mr. Saru.)
MINHO is fast.
(These runners run with gritted teeth.)
(Mr. Saru runs as he glances over at people.)
Come on.
(Gritting his teeth)
(A relaxed smile)
(It's a fierce match between the 3 runners.)
They're fast.
(The group from the netherworld has a fierce match.)
Come on.
(MINHO places 1st!)
Hey.
- Is it MINHO? - So fast.
- MINHO placed first. - For goodness' sake.
(Disappointed)
- So fast. - I won't do short-distance running.
(Sullen)
Where is Dae Ho?
Dae Ho, are you okay?
- Are you okay? - I'm okay.
- Does it hurt? - I'm okay.
- Can you sit? - I'm okay.
I think you're injured.
(A moment ago, after Group 4 set off)
They're fast.
Hey.
(Dae Ho fell down badly.)
(Embarrassed and mortified)
Is that Dae Ho?
He's very embarrassed.
- I'm so embarrassed. - Hurry up.
He's embarrassed.
He's embarrassed. Don't look.
- See if you're injured. - Don't look.
- Don't look. - Don't look.
My goodness.
He probably didn't want us to pay attention to him.
That's right. You should act like you didn't see anything.
I had no idea.
It hurt my pride.
- I'm so annoyed. - A sprint is different.
- A sprint is different. - It's different.
Is there a crew for short-distance running?
Kian84 was fast as well.
I had a feeling that CODE KUNST would beat me.
- That's right. CODE KUNST won. - After all,
he plays soccer five hours a day.
I was always the fastest kid in my classroom when I was young.
- Right? - MINHO made you place second,
- but you're actually very fast. - That's right.
If it weren't for MINHO...
- You would've destroyed them. - How annoying.
- Mr. Saru. - Had we had the event sooner...
Did you look like a monkey when you ran in childhood?
- I was so surprised. - No. Since birth.
- Really? - That clip will go viral.
Mr. Saru.
Let's have the final right away.
Park Ji Hyeon, Ok Ja Yeon,
Lee Jang Woo, and MINHO, please come forward.
- Let's go. - But...
- Ja Yeon, stand here. - Okay.
- Ja Yeon. - Here.
- Ja Yeon, win. Good luck. - Stand there.
(Ja Yeon, good luck.)
She'll start a few meters ahead.
- So fast. - Jang Woo, keep your eyes on this.
- Okay. - Get ready.
He actually looked at the rice.
I think Ji Hyeon might win.
I think it'll be a match between Ji Hyeon and MINHO.
No way. MINHO is too fast.
- Okay. - On your mark.
Let's take the rice home.
- Set... - Jang Woo, good luck.
(Go!)
(They rush forward with a nice start.)
- Look at MINHO. - At first...
Ji Hyeon took the lead at first.
(Ja Yeon doesn't fall behind.)
- Ja Yeon is fast. - She's fast.
- Go! - Ji Hyeon!
(Neck-and-neck)
(Rushing past them)
(Their jaws drop.)
- They're fast. - Gosh.
They're running with gritted teeth.
(They run forward as they stir up the wind!)
(Three runners are leading.)
(What will be the result of the fierce 3-way match?)
Who is the winner?
(They pass the finish line around the same time.)
(MINHO won by a hair's breadth!)
- Who won? - This match...
MINHO!
- MINHO is fast. - MINHO!
- Ja Yeon is fast too. - MINHO...
- won. - She's fast.
I heard the steps behind me.
- He's so fast. - Looking back on my childhood,
girls who looked like her were always fast.
- That's right. - They were fast.
- Tall girls. - That's right.
- Popular girls. - That's right.
A boy like Dae Ho always liked them.
He fell on his down.
The final winner is MINHO.
(The final winner of the 100m sprint is MINHO.)
- Here you go. - I saw that coming.
- It was predetermined. - That's right.
He won the rice he brought.
Thank you.
Let's beat MINHO.
I want to have a match against MINHO right now.
MINHO, have a match against me right now.
He accepted it readily.
- MINHO, run over. - Let's go.
- He's excited. - His stamina is insane.
- He totally sees it as a game. - Seriously.
- Start right away. - Right away.
- On your mark. - On your mark.
(They set off without giving MINHO time to catch his breath.)
(Relaxed)
He's looking at Woo Il while running.
- He's totally relaxed. - He's running slowly.
- My goodness. - He's fast.
- Woo Il. - He's fast.
- He's fast. - MINHO won easily.
Look at that. He's like a machine.
- Next person. - MINHO, I'm next.
- MINHO, run over here. - Run.
Next person.
Look at him. He's running over.
- MINHO is excited. - Keep going until someone wins.
Hurry up.
- I won't lose, okay? - My goodness.
- Oh, my. That's madness. - Look at his eyes.
Oh, my.
Hurry up.
- Hurry up. - For goodness' sake.
(Moomoo, the king of fouls)
(Glancing over)
Hurry up! MINHO, get him!
(I beat MINHO in a sprint.)
(Panting)
The real Lucifer won!
You're pathetic.
- You're pathetic. - I'm happy since I got that shot.
- Listen. - That was what you wanted.
You're faster than MINHO.
- That's right. - I'll cut out that part...
- My goodness. - and upload it on social media.
You're the only one who beat him.
- The young 40-year-old. - The only one who beat MINHO.
That's right.
"Lucifer" is mine.
- How annoying. - You beat MINHO.
- He took "Lucifer." - He finally took it.
That really helped with digestion.
- I know. I'm totally hungry. - I'm hungry.
That's right. I was hungry.
We hadn't had breakfast.
- Hyun Moo, let's eat. - I'm really hungry.
- I'm hungry. - Let's eat.
- Now, the next event. - Seriously.
Let's eat.
(The next event is eating.)
Where are we eating?
Sit wherever you want.
Shall we move these items?
- Thankfully, the rain stopped. - Sit here.
I know.
I'll eat with people who brought many side dishes.
- Let's share food. - Let's share food.
- One staircase up? - Yes.
- We need to put our legs down. - Okay.
We told you guys the day before.
- We told you guys to pack lunch. - Yes.
I woke up at the crack of dawn and packed lunch.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's eat packed lunch first.
(Shall we eat packed lunch?)
- Oh, my. - I was shocked.
- I packed so many items. - Na Rae, seriously.
It was nothing big.
It's nothing big.
Well done. I can tell that it's nothing big.
Are you sure you didn't pack food as if your life depended on it?
- No. - I wanted to share with everyone.
That's right. It was so nice.
- Look at KEY. - Look at his packed lunch.
(KEY appears with a big bag.)
It's so big.
Why are the two of them competing? Hold on a second.
- It's a match. - Park Na Rae versus KEY.
- We won't need anything else. - This is incredible.
Are Na Rae and KEY having a match?
We won't need to take out our food.
There's a rival company.
- Two catering chefs showed up. - That's right.
Exactly.
He's from Gyeongsang Province, and I'm from Jeolla Province.
- Gyeongsang Province... - That's right.
and Jeolla Province. Is this "Korean Food War?"
- It's a match between provinces. - Yes.
There were two catering chefs.
- That's the most important. - I agree.
In ten years, you won't remember the games.
You'll only remember the food.
- You'll remember what you ate. - I agree. That's a memory.
That's the actual highlight.
I agree.
Who remembers the rankings in the sprint?
- No one. - You just remember...
- your mom's tasty gimbap. - That's right.
- He has a point. - That's right.
- You remember the menu. - That's right.
- Park Na Rae, what did you bring? - What?
Park Na Rae, what did you bring?
He's wary.
As for me...
- You brought a cutting board. - Why is there a cutting board?
How many kimchi containers did you bring?
Hey, she brought a cutting board.
- No way. - I was a bit wary.
To KEY, this is the 100m sprint.
That's right.
(The Lunch Battle of Their Own)
Who brings a cutting board to a field day?
It's just like the springboard.
- Well, - Yes?
I prepared some cold meat.
(I prepared some cold meat.)
The color shows how well it's cooked.
- It's cooked well, isn't it? - Yes.
It's cooked to perfection.
There's cuttlefish with vinegar dressing as well.
I followed my mom's recipe.
- The Jeolla Province style. - It looks amazing.
I went all around Noryangjin for that.
Have some of the fried tofu rice balls.
(Generous Na Rae even shares fried tofu rice balls.)
Give them a try.
I've never seen fried tofu rice balls that plump.
He packs this much just for a taste?
Hey!
Na Rae is just like Auntie Omakase.
Na Rae Omakase.
Did you have time for this?
Who packs cuttlefish with vinegar dressing...
to a field day?
There might be leftovers.
Are you serious, Kim Ki Bum?
I brought some for a taste as well.
What are those blue crabs?
- What? - Look at him.
- Blue crabs? - We won't need more food.
It's for everyone to have a taste.
- He's open-handed as well. - Gosh.
He's open-handed as well.
What is this?
I prepared braised crabs with my grandmother's recipe.
Braised crabs?
(KEY especially loved his grandmother's braised crabs.)
- We were all curious about it. - Right.
Who brings crabs to a field day?
- Gosh. - It was a first for me as well.
They're in season right now.
- Right. They were delicious. - Right.
The crabs were huge as well.
So you brought all of this...
- to share with everyone. - Right.
I ordered 5kg of crabs as I didn't know how many would be here.
- What? - You ordered 5kg of crabs.
- He cooked for four hours. - Right.
Blue crabs are in season right now.
MINHO doesn't know how to cook.
- You cooked for him as well? - I prepared rice for him as well.
I made grilled rice balls...
- and rolled omelets. - They're even grilled.
I brought other dishes as well.
(Amazed)
He's a great friend.
Ki Bum is so nice.
(Ki Bum is so nice.)
Pass it to each person.
It's one crab per person.
- It's one crab per person? - Yes.
- Really? - Of course.
- Each person gets one crab. - Right.
- He wants to bring some home. - Go ahead and take some home.
- It's enough for everyone. - Gosh.
Packed lunches should be packed like Kian84.
- What did he bring? - He brought it just for himself.
That's how it should be.
He brought just enough for himself.
It's fried rice.
(Kian84's seed fried rice)
- You promised me a bite. - What?
- You promised me a bite. - Sure.
(He happened to promise him a bite of his seed fried rice.)
All right. Let's use this time...
to reveal what each of us brought.
(Blinking)
- Where is Dae Ho hiding? - I'm here.
Show us what you've brought.
His bag was switched.
Gosh!
It's bibimbap.
What's wrong with him?
Gosh, that looks awful.
I'm sorry, Dae Ho!
(Dae Ho's strange bag of lunch)
(Gosh!)
It was shocking.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(Feeling embarrassed)
- Bye, Dae Ho! - Bye!
Gosh.
Is it sold like that?
- I made it at home. - You made it at home?
- Well, - It would never be sold like that.
I flew back in the morning after a shoot abroad.
What's the name of the dish?
- It's bibimbap. - It's chow.
Chow?
It's squeezed out to be eaten after cutting the end with scissors.
- It's squeezed out? - It looks stunning.
It should be torn up with the teeth, to be precise.
- So it's a forcing bag? - I will ask for some side dishes.
We won't ask for any of yours, Dae Ho.
You should have some.
What about you, Lee Jung?
My mom and dad packed it for me.
That was touching.
- My mom and dad. - Her parents packed her lunch.
- How cute! Her parents packed it. - Fried tofu rice balls?
My mom and dad made these.
- There's a letter! - Gosh!
Read it for us!
Could you read it for me?
I'm going to tear up.
- Your mother wrote it? - Letters always make you cry.
Right.
"Today is the day of the exciting fall field day."
"We wondered what to pack for you as you asked for a packed lunch."
"The whole family got together and pleasantly thought about..."
- "what to make." - How cute.
- It must be her mother. - "We lived away from each other..."
"ever since you were young."
"We were never able to take good care of you."
"We are full of regret and sorrow based on that."
"We are very proud of you,"
"but you still are the most adorable youngest daughter in our family."
He sounds like a homeroom teacher.
She's a student he cherishes.
He's really harsh on Dae Ho.
But she's a student he adores.
- Dae Ho... - Lee Jung's mother...
is the president of the Parent-Teacher Association.
"Okay, Lee Jung."
"We wish that your outing today..."
"will become a precious memory."
"Enjoy your fall field day!"
"Love Mom, Dad, and your older brother."
Everyone, you must be aware of this.
It's Lee Jung's first time at a field day today.
- Really? - I've never been to one.
Then it must be your first time seeing food like Dae Ho's.
I've never seen that before.
- It's a first in Korea. - He deserves respect though.
(She keeps her first packed lunch and letter safe.)
Check out mine as well!
I brought raw gizzard shad.
- Really? - Raw gizzard shad?
I brought a raw gizzard shad salad.
Gosh, that's lovely.
Here.
Did you make it?
Dae Ho made quite a big reaction.
- His reaction was quite big. - Hold on.
Why are you being like that?
- Gosh. - That's amazing.
Gamtae abalone gimbap.
Gamtae abalone gimbap? Gosh!
- Ja Yeon put in a lot of effort. - She did.
- She put in a lot of effort. - Her food was great.
- Her food was great. - Her food was great.
What did you pack, MINHO?
I brought all of the side dishes my mom made for me.
You brought all of the side dishes?
- Since KEY was bringing the rice. - I brought his rice.
Ki Bum said he was going to bring the rice.
Dae Ho has a lot of rice too.
- Do you need some? - I'm fine.
Gosh.
What about you, Jae Hyeon?
I brought duck salad, meatballs,
- Did you make them yourself? - and beef bone soup.
- Beef bone soup? - Right.
- Did you make everything? - I did,
but the soup leaked.
There isn't a single drop left. All of the soup leaked.
All of the soup leaked.
What is that? It's my first time seeing that.
This is cold meat, Na Rae.
- What is that? - He said it was beef bone soup.
- Warm meat. - It's still warm.
This would be perfect for Bokdol.
- Give it to Bokdol. - Should I do that?
It wasn't seasoned, right?
It wasn't seasoned at all.
(Jae Hyeon's packed lunch can be shared with Bokdol.)
Dogs are often fed beef shank.
All of our packed lunches...
are completely different from each other.
- Right. - Right.
- That's what's fun about that. - That was why I enjoyed that time.
We all packed our lunches based on our characters.
Exactly.
What did you pack, Woo Il?
I packed the freshest things in my house.
- It wasn't something you had. - Right.
Canned food.
Canned food? That sounds fresh.
- The 3-minute instant curry. - The 3-minute instant curry.
There's also Spam.
Spam? That's a fresh meal.
Ju Seung's packed lunch looks really pretty!
- What's that? - My mom packed it in the morning.
- Oh, right. - His mother packed it for him.
Ms. Jeon Gwi Sim.
There are rice balls and fried tofu rice balls.
Why didn't my mom pack my lunch for me?
Your mother is a great cook.
What did you bring, Sung Hwan?
I brought a homemade burger.
It's a burger with shrimp, beef, and hash browns.
- I have one more thing. - What is it?
My best friend Ju Seung.
His mother packed this for me.
Fried tofu rice balls.
Ju Seung brought Sung Hwan's rice balls as well.
Right.
- You should eat all of this. - Right.
(Ju Seung's mother took great care of Sung Hwan from the past.)
There are always those friends.
Their mothers pack food for the friends as well.
(Feeling proud)
Did you not bring anything, CODE KUNST?
- Jang Woo! - The gimbap restaurant ladies...
packed these for me.
- They're like his mothers as well. - Right.
They are mothers of their own children.
(Walking around)
- Jang Woo! - Are you serious?
- Show us what you brought. - I felt so jealous.
- His wife made it for him. - Let's see.
- I'm jealous of that the most. - As I was on a diet,
she packed me some gimbap and side dishes.
- She made them? - Right.
- That's nice. - Gosh.
Right.
- The diet lunch packed with love. - Lunch packed with love.
- How is that diet food though? - Right.
The amount of food shows he's on a diet.
- That much means he's on a diet. - Right.
It's just like fasting for him.
It's Kang Yong's turn!
I brought the braised skate made by my mother.
The braised skate made by his mother!
- Gosh! - But...
- it was frozen. - You had it on the show.
Right. It's the braised skate.
- It wasn't fermented, right? - It wasn't fermented.
(His mother's braised skate that he had during his meals)
Everyone's lifestyle can be felt through the packed lunches.
What did you bring, Ji Hyeon?
I brought stir-fried octopus gimbap.
He also brought something that shows who he is.
- It reminds us of Mokpo. - Gosh.
I made this in the morning.
- Right. - It's so good.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - It's good.
- Be careful. - It's unique.
That's what it's like.
Should I separate the crab for you?
Yes, please.
Pass it to me.
Thank you.
Ja Yeon is nice.
She separated the crabs for all of us.
- Ja Yeon did that? - Yes. Even for me.
Gosh!
(Sitting right next to the friend separating the crab for her)
Separate the middle like this.
Suck the meat out.
Thank you.
Check out Kian84's lunch.
(The Rainbow Club members all share the food together.)
Why didn't you bring a packed lunch?
Did you really not bring anything?
Moomoo didn't bring anything.
I packed a lot of food in case of people like him.
I thought that there would be more than enough food.
I fought with my mom.
- Gosh. - My mom didn't pack my lunch.
The icon of bad sons.
"My mom didn't pack my lunch."
(The icon of bad sons)
- Have some gimbap. - Thank you.
(Fortunately, Hyun Moo gets shared with food from everyone.)
Thank you!
Try some of the skate.
It wasn't thawed enough though.
- I wanted to try the braised skate. - It's good.
Did you finish your kimchi fried rice, Kian84?
- Would you like to try some? - Yes.
- I'm really curious. - It's not that good.
- I'm still curious about your food. - Right.
I felt very grateful for MINHO.
No one was interested in my food, but he asked about mine first.
Did you finish it?
You didn't have much as well.
(I'll try Kian84's lunch as well.)
Could you pass me the wet wipes, Ja Yeon?
Was it made with the same recipe?
It was frozen.
- Give it a try. - What's this?
(Expectant)
Would anyone like some more of this?
I made it with the kimchi in the house.
It's actually fried rice this time.
It tastes a bit weird, doesn't it?
It looked like it would taste strong.
I thought it was going to be really salty.
More than how it tasted,
I loved how he showed interest in my food.
- It brought me to tears. - So you felt touched.
- I was asked twice. - I pretended to be cool about it.
I just indifferently said, "Do you want to try it?"
But inside, I was clapping like crazy.
We all felt grateful when a friend showed interest like that...
during our school days.
- Right. - "What did you bring?"
- That one sentence meant a lot. - Actually,
MINHO wasn't that interested in my food.
- He still asked about it though. - You could tell...
he did that on purpose.
When someone brings food that looks really good,
- everyone goes to that person. - They're all gathered there.
If no one asks about your food...
That guy is athletic and has a great character as well.
Right.
I can eat quickly.
(Shall I give it a try as well?)
It can be mixed with Dae Ho's food.
But mine tastes better.
You will never have this again.
What's wrong? It looks like it tastes strong.
- What was put into this? - Something is up.
(How does it taste for everyone to react that way?)
Gosh.
- Has it gone bad? - It hasn't gone bad.
- Even he won't ask for more. - It's clean.
Would you like some figs?
- The fig was really good. - That was really good.
They tasted different, didn't they? Jeolla Province figs are different.
Gosh, I'll have a fig.
Have some figs.
- There are figs? - There are figs?
- There are figs? - They're from Mokpo?
Gosh, there are figs!
- Rinse your mouth, Dae Ho. - Figs!
They sold a lot of these at Mokpo Station.
- Right. - It's so sweet!
You have to buy these.
Anyone want drinks?
You can't resist those.
- Right. - Definitely.
(Rinsing the mouth with a clean drink after the sweet figs)
Would you like one? Oh, you already have one?
Have some drinks.
- Thank you. - My goodness.
Thank you.
It's good.
It's a drink, but it's easy to drink instead of water.
- Right. It's really clean as well. - Right.
- This is good. - It's really clean.
You add soju to that.
It's a secret.
That's my two-percent secret.
(That's my little secret.)
To help digest the food...
What will we do now?
We can't move onto sports right away.
A congratulatory performance has been prepared.
Special guests are here.
- They are here just for all of you. - What?
Stay seated here.
The special guests will come out to perform.
What? Who could it be?
Today's...
congratulatory performance...
will be performed by...
(The stars of the congratulatory performance)
It's all of you!
- What? - Gosh.
It's basically a talent show.
- Gosh, what? - Are you serious?
It's a talent show!
(Disappointed)
(Are there really no special guests?)
What is this?
(This sounds like fun.)
A talent show? What do I do?
Gosh.
You still should've known about it.
He did whatever he wanted.
So he came up with all of the ideas,
and you just did all the hard work.
That was the only thing he didn't tell me about.
I'm disappointed.
- It's more exciting as a surprise. - Right.
Get ready for the talent show.
For the opening performance...
Na Rae.
How are these thrown out?
- Here. - Please listen to me.
- That's general trash. - He prepared something.
Put everything down for now. CODE KUNST?
- Put it in here. - Put it down.
- No one is listening. - None of them listened.
Everyone, there will be...
Gosh.
There will be a performance.
- Fine. - Fine.
Get rid of the food trash later.
Didn't he prepare things for a magic show?
A magic show?
He must be taking things out from his bag.
No way. What are you saying?
All right.
(Rummaging)
What is that?
(A Rubik's Cube?)
- Is it really a magic show? - A Rubik's Cube?
He must've prepared a magic show.
(You're unbelievable.)
This is Jun Hyun Moo's Magic Show!
(Jun Hyun Moo's Magic Show)
- The Moogic Show. - The Moogic Show.
I went to a magic bar in Apgujeong...
- to learn this trick. - That's impressive.
to learn that trick for four hours.
Do you know how to play with this?
- The Rubik's Cube. - Yes.
Your hand looks weird.
(Super awkward)
- His hand looks so weird. - That looks so suspicious.
Your hand looks so unnatural.
Your face is a bit weird!
My face was always weird.
How long does it take for you to solve this?
- Five minutes! - I don't know how to solve it!
I will...
solve it in less than two seconds.
- Come on! - Gosh!
- In less than two seconds. - Come on!
(Come on!)
(Singing)
(Excited)
Gosh, I'm so excited!
(Brace yourselves.)
Count to three for me.
- One, two, three! - One, two, three!
(Ta-da!)
Ta-da!
(Dancing)
(My goodness!)
- We were such a good crowd. - We were a good crowd for him.
Thank you. This was Jun Hyun Moo's Magic Show!
(This was Jun Hyun Moo's Magic Show!)
How much do you sell that for?
- It's not for sale. - It's not?
(Going through the magician's bag)
Look at that.
What kind of lunatic does that?
Who goes through a magician's bag?
(The Rubik's Cube was stolen from the magician's bag.)
(Ta-da!)
- He was faster! - He was faster!
Hyun Moo learned that for four hours.
Hyun Moo took 2 seconds. CODE KUNST took 1 second.
(The magic show destroyer took over the atmosphere in a flash.)
(That was my trick.)
(Feeling bitter)
Come on.
You're never allowed to go through even a professional's bag.
- What kind of punk does that? - Gosh.
I went through your bag as you weren't a professional.
- Right. - Right.
I wouldn't have done that if you were a professional.
Not even Choi Hyun Woo's bag.
Did you have to look that bitter?
I felt bitter as everyone was looking at CODE KUNST.
We are ready for the next one to perform.
Who will go next?
Gosh, that felt awful.
(Looking away)
(Scratching his head)
Do you want to go, Ko Kang Yong?
(Rolling his eyes)
- Ko Kang Yong. - Ko Kang Yong. Hey!
- Ko Kang Yong! - Ko Kang Yong!
It's always the youngest that has to go.
- Let's go. - I loved his spirit.
His spirit was great.
Nice one.
I have a special talent.
- It already sounds exciting. - As for me,
I'm sure there won't be anyone with more chin fat than me.
- I'm confident in that as well. - Here!
- I'm confident. - Here!
Gosh!
(There are many fierce competitors.)
He looks like a big toe.
Apologize to me! I won't let that pass!
- What's wrong with a big toe? - Hold on.
There's the Mouth of Truth in "Roman Holiday."
- Right. - Are you serious?
The Mouth of Truth.
Gosh.
Here I go.
You haven't seen them yet, right? Here I go.
(Several neck folds appear when pressed.)
- He has a lot. - Neck folds.
- Gosh. - Come on!
- There aren't a lot. - Come on!
No.
Come on!
There's the destroyer again.
Count them.
- Hey! - Count them.
- I'll end the game. - Okay.
Gosh!
- Gosh! - How would you beat him?
That was unbeatable.
What?
(He has more neck folds than me?)
Look at Kang Yong's eyes.
(Very flustered)
- That's shocking. - Right.
(His shocking acts unfold before everyone's eyes.)
CODE KUNST takes the win!
- Right away? - There was no need to count.
He had so many.
Agreed.
- He has more? - A lot more.
(Dispirited)
Gosh.
He has so many!
He's the talent show destroyer.
Why do you keep destroying everyone's performances?
He's a destroyer.
He took away everyone's talents.
He even destroyed the magic show.
That mean monkey.
But no one can beat...
- a thousand layers. - Never.
I thought it was one of those pie crackers.
(Feeling proud)
Kang Yong is returning to his seat looking very bitter.
That was it, Kang Yong?
- Sorry? - That was it?
I'll go again after a round.
I had to go up so suddenly.
The performers gain nothing.
It seems like Ju Seung is getting ready to perform.
Ju Seung is getting ready to perform?
I brought these.
- Really? - What did you bring?
Gosh!
Are you serious? He was prepared for this?
- What? - What?
- He really brought them. - That's amazing.
Please come out to the front.
- Toss this up for me. - This part is a must.
I'll hit it accurately.
You'll hit this when this gets tossed?
- I'll surely hit it. - Really?
That won't be easy.
It's hard to hit things with those.
All right. I'll toss it.
It's about to begin.
(Fancy skills)
- Gosh, what's going on? - What's going on?
It started to rain.
Move out!
Why is it raining all of a sudden?
Gosh.
- Why is it raining? - Gosh!
- Ju Seung! - It started to rain so much.
No one is watching.
(No one is watching.)
- We should use the plastic bags. - It's pouring all of a sudden.
Gosh, my legs hurt.
(They all cleaned up together.)
- We can clean up quickly together. - Of course.
To be honest, the performance was just a joke.
An amazing guest will really be coming.
- Gosh. - Really?
Gosh.
Really? Who could it be?
The true star of the day.
- I can't see anything. - Come on in!
Who could it be?
I see something coming!
- Where? - What?
- It's coming! - It's coming!
It must be a stage.
- President Jun. - Old Money.
- Who is that? - It's this grand?
Is it a stage?
What is that?
- What is that? - What is that?
I paid for it.
This is Moosain Bolt's treat!
(This is Moosain Bolt's treat!)
I asked Napoli Matfia for his help.
- What? - These are the popular...
- chestnut tiramisu cakes! - I love it!
I love it!
I'll try the different flavors.
- They look delicious! - They look delicious!
There must be two flavors.
(They all love it.)
Tiramisu and pistachio.
It isn't raining anymore. The rain stopped.
- It stopped as we're about to eat. - Right.
That was fascinating.
- Gosh, Ju Seung. - It stopped raining...
when the talent show ended.
It was fascinating.
- It's gold! - It looks good.
It's gold.
- Give it a try first. - Go ahead.
We can all eat together.
- Thank you! - Thank you!
It was given right when there was a need for sugar.
- Right. - You have to eat a lot at once.
(Thanks to President Jun...)
- It was made in the morning. - It's so good.
The pistachio one is really good.
It was really good.
- I wanted everyone to try it. - I loved it.
- The timing was great as well. - Right.
I felt really grateful.
Jang Woo looks really happy.
- You look happy. - It's good.
The cake tastes great, but don't you all feel thirsty?
- Yes. - Yes.
There's more?
- The special event match! - What is it?
What is it?
The soda drinking contest will commence!
(Another event match, soda drinking contest)
Here!
- He planned for that as well. - For this one,
anyone can participate.
- It's an individual match. - Really?
It's an individual match.
Does the winner win rice for this one as well?
- It's rice. - That's nice.
It's for 20kg of rice.
Just rice? Okay.
(The prize is 20kg of rice.)
All contestants should come to the front.
Why bring a game made for me?
No one can beat Jang Woo.
Bring it on!
(The winner of the beer contest at the baseball park)
Gosh, that's so fast.
(Contestant 1)
Jang Woo will win.
(Lee Jang Woo)
- Dae Ho is really fast. - I'm good at this.
I'm good at drinking fast.
Right.
Go!
(The man who took over the wedding ceremony with beer)
- Right. This happened. - Right.
- That was at the wedding. - Right.
(Contestant 2)
(Kim Dae Ho)
Dae Ho is great at drinking fast.
Dae Ho has to prove himself.
Do well with this one.
It's a big match.
To Jang Woo, this is like running to MINHO.
- These three are competing? - This is just a pig.
(Ku Sung Hwan appears.)
(Everything he grabs goes into his mouth.)
I'm not fast.
- You're not fast. You eat a lot. - I eat a lot.
(Contestant 3, Ku Sung Hwan)
I want to join in as well.
- Ahn Jae Hyeon! - Really?
Let's do it together.
I didn't expect Jae Hyeon to join in.
(Cold drinks are against survival of the man with deficiency heat.)
The cat is faster than him.
Okay. Me too.
You never know how things will go.
(The frugal coffee collector)
He just wants an extra drink.
He wants a free drink.
- That can't happen. - No.
(I will take home any leftovers.)
You have to finish it completely.
A whole bottle has to be finished?
You have to shake the bottle above your head after you're done.
- Does it matter? - The fizz will disappear.
These games are fun to watch.
(The battle between 5 contestants for 20kg of rice)
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Get ready.
You have to shake the bottle above your head after you're done.
(Start!)
(Downing at the same time)
Look at Jang Woo!
- Look at Jang Woo! Gosh! - Gosh, look at Jang Woo!
What's with Dae Ho?
(The soda is poured down almost vertically.)
- It's Jang Woo! - Gosh!
(Choking and stopping)
- It's Jang Woo! - Woo Il just wanted a drink.
(Disappointed)
- No! - Dae Ho!
- Sung Hwan couldn't do it as well. - I couldn't do it.
Look at Jang Woo!
(The two are still unshaken.)
Look at that.
- Look at Jang Woo! - No!
Dae Ho!
(Dae Ho wins by a small margin.)
- Gosh! - What's with Dae Ho?
- He's so fast. - He's so fast.
It was an unexpected result.
(Burping)
(They let out big burps at the same time.)
It's "Jurassic Park."
That was amazing.
- How is that possible? - Gosh.
Jae Hyeon is still drinking.
(Jae Hyeon is still in his lonely fight.)
Is Jae Hyeon at a cafe?
(Shaking)
That's like an IV drip.
Why did he bother to join in?
(Spitting out)
All of a sudden? What's wrong, Jae Hyeon?
What's wrong, Jae Hyeon?
Are you okay, Jae Hyeon?
This isn't possible.
(Choking)
Get back here, Jae Hyeon.
(Feeling pity)
(The great challenge of the man with deficiency heat)
- It was a battle of his own. - His face puffed up even more.
- Right. - He wanted to finish the race.
- Kim Dae Ho wins! - Yes!
(Drinking contest winner, Kim Dae Ho)
Dae Ho is amazing.
- Get back to your place. - Gosh, that was amazing of him.
You're the winner.
(The Palm Oil Prince accepts his defeat.)
Gosh, Dae Ho.
The rice will be handed to Dae Ho!
(The winner wins 20kg of rice.)
- It feels like a town contest. - Right.
Does that make an appeal for one's manliness?
No!
(I won!)
Before we start with the team match,
we will go with another special match.
Why are there so many special matches?
But why are there more special matches?
Didn't we do around 350 special matches?
I'm most excited about this match out of all the matches.
- What could it be? - What is it?
It's ssireum!
(Another special match, ssireum)
This will be fun to watch!
They're huge!
Gosh.
The heavyweight class.
These two are the only ones who can compete with each other.
- Right. - Right.
The weight class is very important for ssireum.
- Right. - Definitely.
Watch your shoulders.
This is the Baekdu class.
(They look like they are competing to become the Baekdu champion.)
- Get ready and go! - Their size could be felt.
- Let's go! - Go!
They look like buffaloes.
(The beasts clash against each other right from the start.)
(Who will become the winner of the intense battle?)
(Next episode)
(Ringing)
(Messy hair)
I'm a musical theater writer.
(Hue Park is back.)
(The writer of the musical "Maybe Happy Ending")
(Hue showed his life as a true New Yorker.)
(His New York life got a great response.)
(He continues to start his day with some coffee.)
(Has his house changed?)
(This is his new house and it has been 3 weeks.)
(This is not New York.)
(It's Seoul!)
Alexa.
(Alexa won't answer back no matter how much he calls for her.)
The Internet isn't working at all.
(He's still unfamiliar with his life in Seoul.)
(I'm so busy.)
(He hurriedly heads somewhere.)
This is confusing after only being on the subway in New York.
(The place he arrives at...)
(is a lecture hall?)
"Who would watch that?" Everyone said this.
(Endless words of advice for the youth)
This can only be done in your 20s.
(Everyone wants to see him even after the lecture.)
(Thank you.)
(Maybe Happy Seoul Life)
(The field day isn't over yet.)
(The competition continues.)
(Ok Ja Yeon turns into Kim Yeon Koung.)
(Bacterrius goes wild with his topknot.)
(Mine!)
Look at their eyes.
(Full of madness)
(The members become one under the sloppy weather.)
(Harmonious)
(Smiling)
It's really different.
(Grabbing her arm tightly)
(Let's go together.)
(Unpredictable)
(Full of laughter)
What happened?
(A great time as they are gathered together)
(Let's go together.)
(Meanwhile, the atmosphere becomes serious.)
MINHO wins!
(Runner84 loses the 100m race to Fiery MINHO.)
(I will get my revenge during the relay race.)
Go!
(Immersed)
(Running at full speed)
(Holding his head)
(You will end up in tears.)
(The Best Runner in This Area)